It says Uaua.
(Laura)
- Is it Laura?
- Yes.
- Let's see.
- Show it to mom.
- No, it says Alma.
- It's UAUA!
Yes, okay.
She very much wants this pink stamp to be her stamp.
UAUA!
We are trying to record this video with a new camera.
Yes.
- A new camera.
So if picture or sound is a little different, then you know why.
And so there were so many so we couldn't answer everyone, but we read everyone.
And then you can take the opportunity to thank now, even though it has gone ...
A few months.
- Yes.
Thank you for sharing.
- Really nice.
It means a lot.
- We probably haven't told us where we are going.
- No.
I have put on my most uncomfortable clothes, because we will actually go and buy a Christmas tree.
- Me too!
- You too.
Yes.
Although we will only buy a Christmas tree.
I want a plot.
- A Christmas tree and a plot.
It is enough.
- It is enough!
- Is this the Christmas tree we should buy?
- No, I think it's just too big.
This one cannot take on the train.
This is probably one of those silver spruce too ...
... which certainly holds very well, but I think it will cost half a fortune.
When we were here the other day she had a lot of fir trees, which is why we went back here.
And now it just seems that the most expensive and finest Christmas tree remains.
But we must probably ask.
- Although she has a small deal there, she may have more.
- Yes exactly.
- Should we go and check out?
- We go and look.
(Portuguese) - Hi, do you have other Christmas trees?
- I have it, and one that is closed.
- There.
- Well.
Okay.
Piff and puff are allowed to stay here.
They must not come along.
Portuguese piff and puff.
- They come along.
- No, they must not come home.
They come along!
Oh...
You are a good negotiator, Laura.
But I do not know.
We get to consult with the rest of the family.
We got the Christmas tree home, but not the same day we were there but the day after that.
And then it went another day because it had to stand here and just get used to the indoor climate.
Yes.
And I needed to move some houseplants and so on.
But now this one is and it is huge.
- It's huge.
- Yes.
Awesome, that is.
Now I see that you are looking at yourself on the screen.
Axel, help me so he doesn't see it.
That with a new camera ...
Then I have to spin around it.
- Gosh!
And then I have to do this, then.
- Yes.
But tomorrow you have school closure.
- I have to see the picture of myself.
- Nämen, stop!
How does it feel to you, Alma?
So, it is a bit boring and a little fun, because it is like the end of something, but also the beginning of something else.
- Yes.
You finish in this school.
- We get to see how it gets.
- Yes.
- Yes, we really get to see.
Where is Laura now?
Laura is on her crèche, ie kindergarten, so ... and she has barely eaten in the middle.
I know.
So we have some home time without her.
Yeah!
- Are you happy with it?
- Yes, quite.
- She takes up quite a lot.
- mm.
Quite.
- Okay, she takes a lot of space.
- Very much space.
We paid 80 \ Heuro for this Christmas tree.
There is a lot of money here in Portugal, but they do not have fir trees here in the same way we have up the north.
- But what does a spruce cost in Sweden?
- Yes, what does a spruce cost in Sweden?
I have no idea anymore.
- Comment below, or what?
- Yes, you must say.
Comment on what a spruce ...
- Are we robbed with our type of 900 kroner spruce?
- With home delivery.
Yes maybe.
But it is worth it for a little Christmas atmosphere.
Yes, but what about the Christmas atmosphere?
Alma, you who stand here barefood and go in shorts and so on.
So ... like that.
But I don't really think the Christmas atmosphere is snow.
Huh?
It is clear that Christmas atmosphere is snow.
So, it is a big deal, and cold too, though like, the Christmas mood is so much more too.
- Do you have a Christmas mood, Harry?
- No not at all.
And what is it, then?
So ... mostly because we kind of are in a very hot country.
It doesn't even snow.
It's just sunny outside.
It's sunset.
- Hello.
- Hello Hello!
(Alma) TA-DA!
It's the Christmas tree, Laura.
- Gosh!
- Did you get shy now?
Hello ... friend!
Did you get a little shy ... for the Christmas tree?
Or what happened there?
Thus, God what a "fail."
(failure) We thought she would be surprised.
- "Give me it, then."
- Well, now you should start going and picking.
Should you sit in my lap?
You're so funny.
You can check it.
There are many nice lights in the Christmas tree.
And lots of balls and packages and socks.
- What do you have there?
- corn.
It's a new day again.
- And Alma and Harry are at school closure.
- Yes.
- We were not allowed to participate in it.
- No.
Boring, but it can be sometimes.
And Laura, she is in kindergarten.
Every year we get the same today's question from several.
We have already received it on Instagram, and that is what the kids should get in Christmas.
Yes.
We understand that it is exciting.
I kind of wanted to have this now, but yes ... so it is to him.
Alma has wanted such a set of "rhinestones."
I don't know if you see it through the plastic, but there are small crystals that you glue on ...
In lots of different colors.
... on type mobile shell, or you can put them on bags, shoes and so on.
Here is some applicantor and here is a big tweezers that belongs.
She's a great point on this so, yes ...
It will be interesting to see what her shoes look like later.
- Yes.
These were the three gifts that we feel we can show.
- And now we're going to hit them.
- Yes, we will.
Once upon a time, I was very good at wrapping packages because I worked at NK as a clerk.
But yes.
No longer.
- You lost it a bit.
- Yes, God.
Are you kidding?
We had to take a package wrapping course, we who worked at NK.
- Because it would go fast or be neat?
- Because it would be beautiful.
So, what is this strange picture?
You just see the bed.